NGUYEN VAN TUAN

BACK-END DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am a final year student majoring in information technology at Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HUTECH). I am willing to learn and experience new things from the company. In a work environment, I can work well individually or in groups. I think your company will be a good environment for me to contribute. Please take your time to check out my resume.

EXPERIENCE

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Feb 2023 - March 2023 | PROJECT: API_SELLCLOTHES_NODEJS_MONGODB

- Write Api in Javascript on Nodejs
- Use Express framework to support writing api
- Manage databases through MongoDB using Mongoose library
- Encrypt, decrypt and generate tokens using the Bcryptjs and Jsonwebtoken libraries
- Guihub: https://github.com/FTeambyDinhPhuc/API_SellClothes_NodeJS_M ongoDB/tree/BranchOfTuan

BACK-END DEVELOPER

April 2022 - May 2022 | PROJECT: APIMESSAGE

- Write Api in Javascript on Nodejs
- Database management through Mysql database management system using mysql library
- Use Express framework to support writing api
- Generate tokens using Jsonwebtoken libraries
- Guihub: https://github.com/tuanbie/ApiMessage

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022 | PROJECT: DACN

- Using C# to handle backend.
- Build database using SQL sever.
- Project structure according to the MVC model.
- Has handling of some web interfaces.
- Github: https://github.com/lamGroot2001/DACN/tree/vantuan_dev



CONTACT

W November 6, 2001

tuansk1002@gmail.com

• 54, district 12d, Long Thanh My, Thu Duc city

**** 0373272294

facebook.com/tuanbie201

github.com/tuanbie

EDUCATION

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (HUTECH) September 2019 - now

 Senior in Information Technology

• GPA: 3.19/4.0

SKILLS

Nodejs

JavaScript

C# .NET

OOP

PERSONAL SKILLS

TEAMWORK

PRESENT, SELF LEARNING

GOOD COMMUNICATION